剪刀石头布
Okay, Rock Paper Scissors.
输的人去第12桌穿短裤的客人说
Loser has to ask the guy in gym shorts at table 12
请停止莎朗·斯通[分享]他的蛋蛋
to stop Sharon Stoneing us his balls.
从我们得进行这对话来说
By virtue of having this conversation,
咱俩都是输家吧
aren't we both losers?
瞧瞧是谁从好莱坞回来了
Look who's back from Hollywood.
这不是黑寡妇与詹妮佛·洛佩茨吗
If it isn't ScarJo and J-Lo.
她詹·洛你还沾屎呢
Said the guy from down low.
我能要个签名吗
Can I get an autograph?
哎呀 说错话了 你们还是服务员
Oops, my bad... still just waitresses.
阿憨 别因为我要赚进25万外加一部
Han, don't be upset just because I'm about to make $250,000
以我人生而拍的电影 就眼红吃醋好吗
and have a movie made about me.
阿憨早就有一部以他为原型的电影了
Han already had a movie made about him...
《小[百]货战警》
"Paul Blart: Small Cop."
那你那部电影叫什么
What's your movie called?
《冲进失业区》[冲出康普顿]吗
"Straight Outta A Job"?
说到失业 你现在不能炒我们
Yeah, about that? You can't fire us now.
电影的钱还没到手
The money hasn't come in just yet.
等进账了 拜托你狠狠炒了我们
After that, by all means, please fire us
使劲儿炒
and fire us hard.
你觉得这个月27号炒我们方便吗
Yeah, how does firing us on the 27th work for you?
别以为我不敢炒你们
Don't think I won't do it.
我想着要新加一个亚裔员工很久了
I've been wanting another Asian in the mix for some time.
对了 阿憨 我们明天要请假
Oh, and, Han, we're gonna need the day off tomorrow.
你们才请完十天假
You just took ten days off!
你们的假用完了
No more vacation days.
不红的明星上班都比你们多
Freddie Prinze Jr. Works more than you two.
我跟麦克斯要去监狱探望我爸
Max and I are going to prison to visit my dad.
因为他的治疗 所以他写了个音乐剧
As part of his therapy, he's written a musical,
他要跟其他狱友一起演出
and he's performing it with the other inmates.
监狱里的音乐剧吗
A musical in prison?
要不是因为我的脖子不行了
I'd be shaking my damn head right now
你会看到我摇头叹气
if my neck still worked.
再说一次 27号那天你就可以炒我们了
And, again, you can fire us on the 27th.
我们现在在过渡期
We're in flux now.
而跟平常一样 最后被"超度"的都是我
And as always, I'm the one who gets fluxed.
我好想[没射中]阿憨啊
Aw, I missed Han.
这是你首次没有十字弓在手时说这句话
I've never heard you say that without a crossbow in your hand.
我等不及那笔钱进账了
I can't wait till we get that money.
快想想我们能买的东西
Think of all the stuff we could buy.
美国制的牙膏
American toothpaste.
厕纸 这样就不用再拿浴室脚垫擦了
Some toilet paper so we can stop using our bath mat.
而且既然我们的信用卡也要被解冻
And since we're unfreezing our credit card,
或许我可以顺便买条新裙子
maybe I'll get a new dress too.
音乐剧邀请函上写了"鸡尾酒会着装"
The invite to this musical said "cocktail attire."
监狱音乐剧还得穿到半正式礼服
A prison musical with cocktail attire?
不管了
Ah, screw it.
我明天肯定有罪受 但是...
I'm gonna feel this tomorrow, but mm, mm!
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
今天是我跟奥列格要知晓
Today's the day Oleg and me find out
以后我们孩子能享受哪种性爱的日子
what kind of sex our baby's gonna have.
我求你换个方式重新说这话
I beg you to rephrase that.
宝贝 我不想知道
Baby, I don't want to know
是男孩还是女孩
if it's gonna be a boy or a girl.
我想把惊喜留到最后
I'd rather be surprised.
就像在墨西哥嫖娼 脱光前不知是男是女
You know, like when you get a hooker in Tijuana.
哇操 汉子
Boy, do I.
哇操 妹子
Or girl, do I.
我们也不知道 这就是乐趣所在
We don't know, and that's the fun.
我们打算找烘焙师
We're gonna have a baker
帮我们做一个揭开性别蛋糕
do one of those gender reveal cakes for us.
你们能介绍个烘焙师吗
Can you guys recommend a baker?
你啥意思呢
Uh, excuse me?
对啊 你啥意思呢
Yeah, excuse me?
什么是揭开性别蛋糕啊
What the hell is a gender reveal cake?
是烘焙完把它裤子扒下来看性别吗
Like, you bake it and then you pull its pants down?
天啊 拜托你
Jeez, would it kill you
偶尔看看美食杂志 是会要你命吗
to pick up a "Rachael Ray Every Day" once in a while?
我们给烘焙师一个写有孩子性别的信封
We give the bakers a sealed envelope with the sex.
然后烘焙师...
Yeah, and then the bakers...
如果我们能找到一个好的...
you know, if we can find good ones...
就会把蛋糕里面的糖衣做成粉色
will make the icing on the inside pink
如果是女孩"斯威特拉娜"
if it's a Svetlana...
蓝色就是男孩"斯威特兰尼"
And blue if it's a Svetlenny.
已经比我波兰老家那里好了
Well, it beats the way they did it in my town in Poland.
你要么是个男孩
You were either a boy
不然你最好知道怎么从井底爬出来
or you had to know how to climb back up out of a well.
你知道我们是烘焙师 对吧
Um, you know we're bakers, right?
对啊
Hell, yeah.
我现在就大麻吸嗨[烘焙]了
I'm baked right now.
我为我爸爸的监狱音乐剧盛装打扮了
Well, I'm dressed for my father's prison musical.
试试说这句话三次而不哭
Say that three times without crying.
很好看啊
You look good.
如果那些犯人本来不是惯犯硬汉
If those inmates weren't hardened criminals before,
看到你之后也肯定成"硬"汉了
they will be once they see you in that.
你拿这些从飞机上偷来的
What's with all the miniature liquor bottles
迷你酒出来干嘛
you stole from the plane?
是不是得给你来个迷你戒酒批斗会
Do I have to host a tiny intervention?
这些不是我从飞机上偷的
I did not steal these from the plane.
我是从酒店房间里 清洁人员推车
I stole them from our hotel room, the maid cart,
以及我假扮成清洁人员 从别人房间偷来的
and a few other people's hotel rooms when I posed as a maid.
而这个 是要展示
This is part of my presentation
我所想出如何花这25万的计划
for my idea on how to spend the $250,000.
五年前 我们坐在栗宝身上
Five years ago, we were sitting on Chestnut
拿着冰咖啡
with our iced coffees.
这段记忆犹如五年前那么久
I remember it like it was five years ago.
我们说只要有25万
And we said that $250,000
正好是我们要拿到的数额
the exact amount of money we're getting,
就足以让我们能做小蛋糕生意
was what we needed to get our cupcake business going.
栗宝当时特兴奋 都拉了一小泡屎
Chestnut was so excited, he made a little poo.
哪是一小泡
Not so little.
我还记得那泡屎把路过的猫打晕了
I remember it knocking that cat unconscious.
而五年后
Five years later,
但凭小蛋糕是活不下去的
cupcakes alone aren't cutting it.
伤人 但在理
Ouch. But true.
的确 它们又甜又好吃又潮
Sure, they're sweet, delicious, and chic,
但如果我们往里面加酒呢
but what if we add... alcohol?
就变成又甜又好吃又贵啦
Which is sweet, delicious, and expensive?
我们保留小蛋糕窗口
We keep the cupcake window,
但再把它变成一家酒吧
but we make it into a bar too.
把两个超赞的东西合二为一
It's two great things put together!
就像我跟你吗
Like you and me?
我本来是想说胖子加跌倒
I was gonna say fat people and tripping,
不过你说得对
but yes!
保留小蛋糕梦
We keep the cupcake dream;
只是加上特贵的酒
we just add overpriced alcohol to it.
我爱这点子
I love it!
我们可以称其为小蛋糕鸡尾酒
We can call it Cupcakes & Cocktails.
如果我们不想显得太讨人厌
Or, if we want to be less douchey,
那就叫做甜点吧
we call it Dessert Bar.
这点子太聪明了
That is a genius idea.
通常你喝醉的时候 你最好的点子就是
Usually when you're drunk, your best idea is,
"打给家居用品店问它们有没有填缝材料"
"Let's call Home Depot and ask if they have caulk."
我们要这么做吗
So we're doing it?
要开一家甜品吧吗
We're opening up a dessert bar?
我们绝对要开一家甜品吧
Oh, we're opening up a dessert bar.
庆祝之舞吗
Celebratory dance?
我到了吗
Am I here yet?
这味道 如果不是麦克斯与卡洛琳家
I know I'm either at Max and Caroline's
就是在爱宠动物园
or a petting zoo.
我先声明 马的味道是沙发传来的
To be clear, that horse smell is the couch.
我刚从医生那里回来
Oh, I just came back from the doctor,
我手里拿着宝宝的性别 但我不想看到
and I have the sex of the baby, but I don't want to see it.
快请你们从我手上拿走 不然我想偷看
So please take it from me quick so I don't sneak a peek.
卡洛琳 这个你来保管
Caroline, you hold on to this
等我要做蛋糕了再给我
until it's time to bake the cake.
你为什么要给她啊
Why are you giving it to her?
你真的觉得她这个
I mean, you really think she can keep a secret
有搞笑艺人大嘴巴般的人能守住秘密吗
with that big Jim Carrey mouth flapping all the time?
你不会想要让我保管
Well, you don't want me to have it.
我一旦知道了 表情藏不住
If I know, I'll spoil it.
我做不出扑克脸
I have no poker face.
我妈也没办法 这也是为什么
Neither did my mom, which is how I became
我是某家赌场的合法财产
the legal property of the Borgata Casino.
卡洛琳 我警告你
Caroline, I'm warning you.
千万别说漏嘴
Don't let it slip.
哪怕我求你 也别告诉我
Even if I beg you, don't tell me.
好的
Okay.
就算我大半夜下楼来你家
Even if I come downstairs in the middle of the night
拿着枪指着你的头
and put a gun to your head,
也别说
don't tell me.
如果事情到了有枪这一步
Okay, well, if there's a gun involved,
我绝对会告诉你
I'm gonna tell you.
麦克斯 你看
See, Max?
这就是为什么我不想让她保管
That's why I didn't want to give it to her.
这部音乐剧你爸编剧加导演吗
Your dad wrote and directed this thing too?
他简直就是监狱版的本·阿弗莱克
Dang, he's like the Ben Affleck of jail.
靠 这里写着
Yikes, it says here
演出"虐待狂警卫"的人
that the guy who was playing "sadistic guard"
今晚无法参与演出
is out for tonight's performance
因为有人拿塑料叉勺挖了他眼珠
because someone took his eye out with a plastic spork.
天啊 这也太惨了
Oh, my God. That's terrible.
我们居然得看替补演员演出吗
We're seeing an understudy?
你看 我爸爸是开场演员
Oh, look! My dad's opening the show.
* 铁窗 *
* Steel bars *
* 我心上的铁窗 *
* Steel bars on my heart *
* 我灵魂的铁窗 *
* Steels bars on my soul *
* 此刑无法假释 *
* And there's no parole *
* 并将我心撕碎 *
* And it tears me apart *
* 铁窗 *
* Steel bars *
* 我蛋蛋的铁窗 *
* Steel bars on our balls *
* 这监狱的铁窗 *
* Steel bars on this jail *
* 而且无法保释 *
* And there ain't no bail
* 没人打来慰问 *
* And nobody calls *
我每周打给他两次呢
I call him twice a week.
* 咱蛋蛋的铁窗 *
* Steel bars on our balls *
* 铁窗 *
* Steel bars *
* 在咱的蛋蛋上 *
* On our baaaaaalls *
太他妈赞了
Oh, hell, yes!
* 25年到终身监禁 *
* 25 to life *
* 疼痛与争执无数 *
* Lots of pain and plenty of strife *
* 孤独如刀般锋利 *
* Loneliness, it cuts like a knife *
* 25年到终身监禁 *
* 25 to liiiiiife *
谢谢 谢谢大家
Thank you. Thank you so much. Wow.
我们不会把各位"关"在这里太久
Well, we won't keep you prisoner much longer.
简短的幕间休息后
So we're just gonna take a brief intermission,
我们将回来演出下半场
and we'll be back with the second half.
什么下半场 刚才都三小时了
Second half? That was three hours!
太棒了 爸爸
That was incredible, Dad!
尤其是试图逃狱的那一幕
Especially the escape attempt scene.
那一幕的暴力场景看起来特别真
Some of that violence looked incredibly realistic.
因为那是真的 不是剧情
That was because it was real, not part of the show.
警卫把那犯人打了个半死
They beat that guy severely.
* 铁窗 *
* Steel bars *
噔噔 什么什么的
Da-dum, something, something.
马丁 我要在你身上加上新的两项罪名
Martin, I'm gonna add two more crimes to your prison sentence:
偷走我的心 与偷走全场目光焦点
stealing my heart and stealing the show.
能在我节目单上签名吗
Can you sign my playbill?
卡洛琳 拿出我的节目单
Caroline, get my playbill.
这里 帮我拿一下苏菲的揭开性别信封
Oh, here. Hold Sophie's gender reveal envelope.
还有这个我拿来当做钱包的信封
Oh, and this envelope I use as a wallet.
还有我拿来当做化妆包的信封
And this other envelope I use as a makeup bag.
在这里
Oh, here it is.
我只能用蜡笔给你签名
Great. I'm gonna use my crayon.
我们不能拥有笔
We can't have pens.
来 也签我的
Oh, here. Sign mine too.
我会把这签名放在我裱框起来
I'll put it next to that framed picture I have
你跟早年还支持自由党的川普合照的照片旁
of you and Donald Trump when he was a liberal.
好了 说够我的事了
Well, enough about me.
谁要在你的电影里演我呢 宝贝
Who's playing me in your movie, hon?
别找布拉德·皮特 太像我了
Not Brad Pitt. It's too on the nose.
他们还没开始选角
Well, they haven't cast it yet,
但他们会付给我25万来买我的故事
but they are giving me $250,000 for my story.
宝贝 这就是你的入门票
Honey, this is your ticket.
你可以开始自己的生意了
Now you can start your own business.
我跟麦克斯有自己的生意了啊
I have my own business with Max.
小蛋糕生意吗
The cupcakes?
我承认生意最近有些淡
I'll admit business has been slow.
但我们会用这笔钱
But we're gonna use the money
把我们的生意带到下一个阶段
to take our business to the next level.
麦克斯有个天才点子 把蛋糕店改成甜点吧
Max had the genius idea of making it a dessert bar.
我们还是会卖小蛋糕
We still sell our cupcakes,
但我们也卖高档鸡尾酒
but we also serve high-end cocktails.
只要加上"混合"这个字
You can just say the word "muddle"
就能卖20块
and charge $20.
姑娘们 这个点子太棒了
That is a fantastic idea, ladies.
棒极了
Wow, it's so great.
亲爱的 能帮我去那点水吗
Honey, do me a favor. Could you get me some water?
我想为明早的戏保持水分充足
I want to stay hydrated for tomorrow's matinee.
道上传闻罗伯特·德斯特专门转狱来看呢
There's talk of Robert Durst transferring in just to see it,
说出来我怕会有"厄运" 就不会实现了
and I don't want to jinx it, you know.
想甩开傻子单独谈是吗
Wanted to ditch the square, huh?
我明白
I get it.
这事终于要来了吗
Is this finally happening?
为庆祝要亲热一发吗
Celebration make-out sesh?
我们得把双手放在他们看得到的地方
Uh, yeah, we got to keep our hands in plain view.
小蛋糕的生意根本不适合卡洛琳
This whole cupcake business is not for Caroline.
做蛋糕的又不是她 是我
Well, she's not the baker; I am.
她负责创意
She's the idea person.
但甜点吧这个点子不是你想的吗
Yeah, but you had the dessert bar idea, right?
而你刚才也说这是一个超棒的点子
And you just said it was a terrific idea.
你也看见了
Well, as you saw...
我是一名好演员
I'm a really good actor.
我能挠挠鼻子吗
Can I itch my nose?
听着 我的宝贝在华尔街长大
Look, my baby was brought up around Wall Street.
接受沃顿商学院教育
She's Wharton bred.
卖小蛋糕这种小生意 永远不可能让她开心
She could never be happy doing this whole baking business,
这次是她解脱的大好机遇
and this is her big chance to get out.
但她难道不会自己跟我说吗
But wouldn't she have told me?
她有任何想法都会跟我说
She tells me every single feeling she's having.
有一些我甚至还听进去了
And some of it, I even listen to.
那如果我直接问她呢
What if I just ask her?
她只会否认
She'll only deny it.
她不想让你伤心
She doesn't want to hurt your feelings.
所以我来帮她说
That's why I'm doing it.
但她说过甜点吧让她开心不已
But she said she was happy about the dessert bar.
我们开心得跳舞了呢
We danced about it.
麦克斯 听我说
Max, listen to me.
我是她爸 我了解她
I'm her father, and I know her.
这次是她的大好机遇
And this is her big chance.
你就放手让她走吧
You just got to let her go.
真的要这样吗
I do?
是的 你一定要态度坚决
Yeah, and you got to be firm about it,
不然她不会明白
or she's not going to get the message.
就像电影《鬼驱人》
Like in "Poltergeist,"
他们不得不严厉管教他们的小女儿
where they have to be really stern with Carol Anne
否则她就会那只鬼厮混在一起
or else she'll stay with the ghosts?
而我就是那只鬼吗
And I'm the ghosts?
麦克斯 你怎么了
Max, what is going on with you?
你没事吧
Are you all right?
没事
I'm fine.
我在给苏菲做性别蛋糕
I'm just making Sophie's gender cake.
如果你不想待在这里 那就回华尔街啊
If you don't want to be here, go back to Wall Street.
什么
What?
你到底怎么回事
What is going on with you?
从我们离开监狱 你就一直气扑扑的
You've been pouty ever since we left the prison.
如果是因为不舍得走所以不爽
I'm not gonna take you there anymore
那下次不带你去了
if you're sad to leave.
你懂个屁啊
You know what?
老娘在忙着干所有的活
While I'm doing all the work,
你去帮我把那个有性别的信封拿过来
why don't you go get me the gender envelope?
好的 易怒的大忙人
Okay, Moody Giuliani.
别告诉我你把那个里面有
Do not tell me you lost the envelope
苏菲宝宝性别的信封弄丢了
with the gender of Sophie's baby in there.
我没有弄丢了
I didn't lose it.
只是它不在我这儿
I just don't have it,
我也不知道它在哪儿
and I don't know where it is.
很可能是你让我把节目单拿出来时
Oh, we probably left it at the prison
不小心把它落在监狱了
when you made me get out the playbill.
所以这是我的错吗
Oh, so this is my fault.
你只需要把这一件事做好 你却搞砸了
The one thing you had to do, you didn't do.
就像素食餐厅里的服务员
Like a waitress at a vegan restaurant,
你端上桌的东西[贡献]跟没有一样
you're bringing almost nothing to the table.
我可是贡献了25万美金啊
The $250,000 I'm bringing to the table,
那也叫没有吗
that's nothing?
所以那是你的钱
Oh, so that's your money.
终于说出来了
There it is.
你何不带上你的钱
So why don't you take your money
滚回华尔街
and go back to Wall Street?
我没关系
I'll be fine.
是谁想出将甜点和酒精结合的绝世好点子
Who came up with combining desserts and alcohol?
显然 一直都是你在拖我后腿好吗
I mean, obviously, you've been holding me back.
是我一直在拖你后腿吗
I've been holding you back?
你参加商业会议时还忘了穿裤子呢
You forgot to wear pants to a business meeting.
这事你也敢说
How dare you?
我明明有穿裤子
I did wear pants.
只是落在厕所了而已
I just left them in the bathroom.
既然如此
Okay, well...
这事都可以载入史册了
Well, this is a historic event.
我们一起卖了五年的小蛋糕
We've sold cupcakes for five years,
这是你第一次碰面糊
and this is the first time you've touched batter.
这的确是该载入史册
It's a historic event
因为你终于想出一个生意点子
because you finally had a business idea
里面不带"屁"字
that didn't have the word "fart" in it.
敢沾到我头发 我们恩断义绝
If my hair gets involved, we are done.
求之不得
Good.
姑娘们 我准备去...
Girls, I'm going to...
你都干了什么
What have you done?
我对鸡蛋过敏啊
I have an egg allergy!
* 25年到终身监禁 *
* 25 to Li... *
见到你真是惊喜
Hey, what a nice surprise.
你知道什么还让人惊喜吗
You know what else is a surprise?
监狱的化妆灯把人照得好美啊
That the makeup lights in a prison are so flattering.
我不记得演出里有他啊
I don't remember him being in the show.
是没他
Yeah, he's not.
他只是个喜欢贴假睫毛的重罪犯
He's just a felon who likes false eyelashes.
你来这里干嘛
So what are you doing here?
我把一个重要的信封落在这里了
I think I left an important envelope here.
我试过给你打电话 但他们说
I tried calling, but they said
你接电话的权利被取消了
your phone privileges were taken away.
是的 我跟监狱的剧评家打了一架
Yeah, well, I had a fight with the prison theater critic.
你真的要起这种破标题吗 艾迪
That's the headline you go with, Eddie?
"跳不出监狱 舞不出人生"
"Shanks for Nothing"?
他在自己博客上肯定形象高大
He sure is a big man on his blog,
但他都不敢直视我的双眼
but he can't look me in the eye.
要我就把标题起为 监狱"暴动"
Well, I would have gone with "It's A Prison Riot."
我好像把一个信封落在这里了
I think I left an envelope here,
因为它 我和麦克斯友谊的小船说翻就翻
and I think it ruined me and Max's friendship
我们合作的巨轮也沉了
and our partnership.
好吧 都在这呢
All right, well, here you go.
这是你的信封
Here's your envelope,
这是你的化妆包
and here's your makeup bag.
听到你和麦克斯搞成这样 我很遗憾
I'm real sorry to hear about you and Max.
除非 这没准是件好事
Unless maybe it's a good thing
这是上天的安排
and it's happening for the best
让你可以回华尔街
and you get to go back to Wall Street
重新过上原本的生活
and reclaim your life.
华尔街
Wall Street?
为什么每一个人都在跟我说
Why does every single person keep telling me
让我回华尔街呢
to go back to Wall Street?
麦克斯 你
Max, you...
好吧 只有你和麦克斯
all right, it's just Max and you.
让我来吧
Here. Let me do that.
听着 亲爱的
Listen, honey.
你只需在华尔街工作 好吗
You only have to work on Wall Street, okay?
你可以生活在上东区
You can live on the Upper East Side
最后搬到韦斯切斯特富人区
and eventually move to Westchester
因为你想要一个网球场
if you want a tennis court.
爸爸 你跟麦克斯是不是谈过这事
Daddy, did you and Max talk about this?
宝贝 我比任何人都了解你
Kitten, I know you better than anybody,
我知道你不属于
and I know that you do not belong
布鲁克林的一个小蛋糕店
in a cupcake shop in Brooklyn.
你还是能和麦克斯做朋友啊
You could still be friends with Max.
她喜欢打网球吗
She like tennis?
你怎么知道我属于哪里
How do you know where I belong?
像这样
Go like this.
我不再是那个曾经被宠坏的富家女了
I'm not the same spoiled little rich girl that I was.
但现在你可以是啦
Well, now you can be.
过去的五年让我脱胎换骨
These last five years have made me a different person.
举个例子 当我走进
For example, when I walk
一家结合墨西哥卷饼和美式甜甜圈的店
into a combination Taco Bell-Dunkin' Donuts,
你知道他们会说什么吗
you know what they say?
"你好 卡洛琳"
"Hi, Caroline."
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
爸爸 我是墨西哥卷饼
See, Daddy, I'm Taco Bell,
麦克斯是美式甜甜圈
and Max is Dunkin' Donuts.
从表面上看 我们俩根本不搭界
On the surface, it seems like we shouldn't be together,
但我们组成了一个完美的团队
but we make an amazing team.
而我们有一个共同的梦想
And we have a dream together.
那不仅仅是她的梦想 也是我的
It's not just hers; it's mine too.
这是我今天最难以接受却又不得不接受的事
Well, that's the hardest thing I've had to take in all day.
午餐时 我们吃的是一坨叫"棕色"的东西
And for lunch, they served us something called "Brown."
听着 爸爸 我就属于这里
See, Daddy, this is where I belong.
不是指监狱 虽然我会想念这里的灯光
Well, not here, even though I will miss the lighting,
但我离不开麦克斯
but with Max.
我想我可以支持这一点
I guess I can support that.
听着 我道歉 对不起
Look, I'm sorry. Sorry.
因为我担心你 好吗
You know, I worry, okay?
父母都这样
That's what parents do,
而且当身在监狱 你会有大把时间担心这担心那
and there's lots of time to worry when you're in prison,
所以我把我所有的精力
which is why I focused all my energies
都用于创作开创性的音乐剧
on creating groundbreaking musical theater.
你确定你没告诉你爸
Are you sure you didn't tell your dad
我告诉了你 是他告诉我让我这么告诉你的
that I told you that he told me to tell you that?
因为告密者会不得好死
'Cause snitches get stitches.
我爸连只苍蝇都不忍心伤害
My dad wouldn't hurt a fly.
他只会偷走它十亿而已
He'd just steal $1 billion from it.
我第一个蛋糕做得还不错吧
Not bad for my first cake, right?
如果不算我扔进垃圾桶的那些
Well, if you don't count all the ones I threw in the garbage.
我算过了 一共七个
I did count them. There were seven.
其中两个还发出了气泡声
Two of them were fizzing.
但至少你努力过了
But thanks for trying.
麦克斯 卡洛琳 快点
Max, Caroline, come on!
这需要多长时间
How long is this gonna take?
当年等研发小儿麻痹疫苗都没等这么长
I didn't wait this long for the polio vaccine.
小儿麻痹居然有疫苗吗
There's a polio vaccine?
你们可能还得再等一会
Well, you might have to wait a little longer
才能知道宝宝的性别
to find out the sex of the baby,
因为我和麦克斯有个新的生意通知要宣布
because Max and I have a new business announcement too.
是关于我解雇你俩吗
Is it about me firing you?
因为我已经为你们的"解脱万岁"派对
Because I already reserved a karaoke machine
预定了一台卡拉OK
for your Good Riddance party.
不是让你取消掉 但你不能解雇我们
I'm not saying cancel it, but you can't fire us
等我们的新生意经营顺利后才许解雇
till we have our new business idea up and running.
《丁字裤之歌》是我的 谁都不许抢
And I'm talking dibs on the "Thong Song."
好啦 我们的大好消息来了
All right, so here's our big news.
我们应该去花蕾烘培坊定这个蛋糕
We should have gone to Rosebud's Bakery for the cake.
因为你在那里定蛋糕
You know, 'cause when you order one there,
他们不会废话说 "猜猜我发生了什么"
they don't say, "Hey, guess what happened to me!"
真俗气 卡洛琳
Pretty tacky, Caroline.
你一个穿着过气动作男星
Says the guy in a tank top
为平价百货设计的背心 还有脸说我
from the Steven Seagal for Target collection.
我现在没什么信心说这事了
Now the wind's out of my sails.
才没有呢 我们要开一间甜点吧
No, it's not! We're opening a dessert bar!
好了 把刀给我
All right, give me the knife.
是切蛋糕吗
To cut the cake?
不是
No.
那我不会给你
Well, then I'm not gonna give it to you.
我在这餐厅说了无数遍这话
Like I said at this diner a million times,
"给我" 卡洛琳
give it to me, Caroline.
好了 宝贝 你来切蛋糕
Okay, baby, you do the honors.
为什么非得知道宝宝的性别呀
Why do we need to know the gender anyway?
现在性别都能变来变去了
They all switch 'em now.
好了 一 二 三
All right, one, two, three.
男孩还是女孩
Boy or girl?
白色 那是什么意思
It's white. What does that mean?
意思是孩子有机会
Well, it means it has a chance
被提名奥斯卡
of getting nominated for Academy Awards.
糟糕
Oh, no!
我忙着扑灭烤箱手套的火
I was so busy putting out that oven mitt fire,
忘了给蛋糕胚加颜色了
I forgot to put the color in it.
但我可以直接告诉你们
But I could just tell everybody.
不必 因为如果从你嘴里得知
No, 'cause if I hear it from you,
我会现在就不爽我肚子里的孩子
I'll already be mad at the baby.
算了 苏菲
You know what, Sophie?
或许这是上帝的旨意
Maybe it's a sign
我们不该知道宝宝的性别
that we shouldn't know what the baby's gonna be.
你说得对
You're right.
蛋糕你们自己留着吧
Keep the cake, girls.
我们不会付钱的
We're not gonna pay.
你们想尝尝吗
Well, do you guys want to try it?
不了
No, thanks.
晚上有女人要来我家
I've got a lady coming over.
我们要尝试弄懂网络电视怎么用
We're gonna try to figure out how Netflix works
然后"干"点别的
and chill.
我也有女人要来我家
I also have a lady coming over.
没错 是来伺候我雪貂的拉拉按摩师
Yes, it's a lesbian masseuse for my ferret,
但这也算啦
but it counts.
我猜你是唯一一个
I guess you're the only one
品尝我第一个蛋糕的人
who's gonna taste my first cake.
我也有女人要来我家 吧
I also have a lady coming over, question mark.
来嘛 就尝一口
Come on. One bite.
麻烦打电话叫救护车 谢谢
Could you dial 911, please?